I can hear the sound of the light's heart.
It says it's heading home.
It's similar to my journey's goal.
Mosk...
Is there something there that I want?
And what is that "something"?
Now that even the food has run out,
all that awaits me
is a solitary death.
Alone...
just...
Vince!
Something's blinking!
Over that way!
They might be card soldiers, you know?
You're talking about the picture book, aren't you?
I'm not alone, after all.
I have company...
though she's an infected autoreiv.
Light!
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
A tower?
If we hide in its shadow...
we might avoid the attacks from above.
From our current position, go 558 units along the x-axis,
832 units along the y-axis, and-
Shut up and help!
Autoreivs?
Pino.
Don't move!
Okay.
Have the Mosquito track down the enemy!
Hey, is it yummy?
So it lies ahead of here, this dome-shaped city?
It's Romdeau.
Card soldiers?
What's that?
We saw a light.
That's why we came.
Light...
The same nonsense she talks about.
The legend about some monster that's sleeping underground?
That's just a legend.
There's no truth to it.
But why are you fighting the autoreivs?
"Why..."?
Such doubt will cost you your life on the battlefield.
I don't get it.
So it's true that when they get
infected by that virus, they develop a heart.
I'm sorry.
That's enough.
But I-
We are only travelers.
Not only did you save us, but you fed me.
I thank you for that.
You sure can eat.
I'll believe you.
I'm Vincent.
Vincent Law.
Note: In Aztec mythology, Omacatl was a god of feasting, holidays and
happiness, and an aspect of Tercatlipoca, the god of the night.
I am the adjutant, Omacatl.
Note: In Aztec mythology, Patecatl was a god of healing and fertility.
With Mayahuel, he was the father of the Centzon Totochtin.
This is Commander Patecatl.
By the way, about that sail ship...
The Centzon?
What is its power source?
What is its average speed and cruising range?
I don't know the specs of the ship that well.
I don't know, either.
Don't worry.
My subordinates are retrieving it.
Let us handle repairs.
Thank you for everything.
Repay us by working.
Fight with this.
Um...
No sign of the enemy near Haros.
Good.
Damage report.
Alpha, Beta, and Gamma squadrons have nine casualties.
Our battalion currently has 43 men.
Please order additional production.
We aren't so desperate for new
men that we'd use valuable energy
when we're in a war of attrition.
Understood.
Everyone, stop what you're doing and listen up.
I'll start off with bad news.
We lost nine comrades in the last battle.
However, there is no need to fear.
The enemy has one target:
the fortress' core and our production center, the artificial womb.
Although they may seek to overwhelm us with their numbers,
so long as they have only one target,
their patterns of attack are predictable.
Once we retrieve the sail ship, start tuning it up and arming it.
What?
In war, there is no room for restraint.
Besides, with its mobility and fuel
efficiency, that ship will be quite useful in battle.
Y-Yes...
We humans must win.
As a human, you understand that well, right Vincent?
Things have become complicated.
Um...
Where is the restroom?
I'm sorry.
This is B-4.
Requesting permission to land.
How pathetic.
Vince?
Maybe my stomach couldn't take eating so suddenly.
I'm fine now.
Fine, fine.
For some reason, I felt that I'd somehow gotten closer
to the autoreiv with a heart.
Feelings that I didn't have when it
was just the two of us traveling together.
I...
just wanted to see someone.
Something's weird.
The people here.
Yeah.
Once the ship's repairs are complete,
maybe we'll make a run for it when we have a chance.
I finally made it to Haros.
But here too, I did not belong.
Pino?
What's the matter?
Something blinked.
Again?
There's nothing down there.
But it went... "blink blink".
We're going.
Okay.
A sail ship?
Never seen that particular model before.
Well, it's nice that we don't have
to worry about the power source.
Considering the Mosquito's cruising range,
this will be very useful.
Hey.
Please, tell me.
What's going on?
I-
Who else could it be?
Asura's soldiers wouldn't kill like that.
It's as though...
the killer enjoys what he does.
Ridiculous.
Why would I-
Then it's that autoreiv.
Impossible.
All we know for certain
is that such things never happened until you guys came.
Wait!
It's not me!
It's happened again...
Am I...
Death?
Whenever I get involved, there's always bloodshed.
Everyone dies...
Miss Re-l...
What do you think of them?
They said something about a light.
The women said the same thing too.
Is this more nonsense about the moonlight we can't see?
Are you saying we should believe such foolishness-
Either way, if this will prevent more deaths...
Commander, the Asura forces...
I am seeing more and more.
I am hearing more and more.
I am getting stronger and stronger.
After...
a ringing sound is heard everywhere,
the lord shall finally come with the
moonlight that floats within the darkness.
Slowly...
he shall come.
Gradually...
Maybe...
without even realizing it...
Gradually...
something inside of me has...
This sensation...
Gradually...
I can hear...
the heartbeat... of beginning.
Gradually...
With the moonlight that floats within the darkness...
give us time of the absolute.
The heartbeat of beginning.
After a ringing sound...
the lord shall finally come
under the moonlight.
Vince?
No...
Help me...
I don't want to change...
Into what?
Into something...
Into anything...
No!
Area 32 has been breached!
The Asura forces
consist of approximately 30 squadrons.
They are advancing towards Area 15.
They must be after the Mosquito.
All men to your stations!
Defend the Mosquito at all costs!
Also, position two units near the artificial womb.
All remaining men, head for the heliport!
No...
Please stop it.
Commander.
An Asura squadron has infiltrated the basement facility
and just now has-
So soon...
Bastard, you're going to escape by yourself?
Not all of us can get on anyway!
We can't rebuild our forces without the artificial womb, either!
Shit.
Hurry up and get us out of here!
Is that what the woman was talking about?
It's just like the legend says?
A direct hit!
Eat shit!
Hurry up and take off!
W-Wait!
Senex...
The proxy of moonlight...
The heartbeat of battle...
What it sounds out...
is a melody that announces the birth
of a new world...
The lord shall come
with the moonlight
that floats within the darkness...
How beautiful...
After that battle...
he shall bestow absolute death to our world...
Who are you?
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
Ninety-seven rabbits.
Ninety-eight rabbits.
Ninety-nine rabbits!
One hundred rabbits!
Okay!
I already counted to one hundred,
meditation  shard of
brilliance
so I'm going to leave Vince behind, okay?